A Guide to the Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company Records, 1836-1943
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Records, 1886-1898., Extent: 16 items.
  - Proposal, Reuben Shirreffs, Richmond, Virginia, to Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company, Old Dominion Nail Works Company, The Haxall Crenshaw Company, et. al., 6 December 1892., 3 items (Folder c)
    Calculations for development and improvement of water power at Richmond [see 755.44/H9/1892(1)].
  - L. P. Reder, Lynchburg, Virginia, to John A. Harris, n.p., 21 December 1892 and 29 December 1892, with note from F. J. C., n.p., to F. B. Isaacs, n.p., 30 December 1892., 3 items (Folder d)
    Map of Lynchburg showing proposed route of culvert and procurement of right of way [See 755.59/Rl5/[1892]].
  - Typescript copy, assessment of the value of the land of John Hogan, Rockbridge County, Virginia, condemned for use of North River Navigation Company, recorded 9 June 1853. Typescript probably 1895., 1 item (Folder e)
    [See 755.812/C2/1895].
  - Notes and calculations concerning James River locks and relative efficiency of undershot and breast water wheels, ca. 1898., 4 items